

IRFAN FAIRUZ @ VIKY

- Freelance Developer
- Based in Malaysia
- Born in 1996

Professional Summary

Highly skilled and motivated web developer with years of experience in front-end and back-end development.

Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS & JavaScript with a focus on creating responsive and UI/UX friendly websites & web applications with efficient technologies.

My main stacks are NextJS with TailwindCSS for Frontend and NodeJS with ExpressJS for Backend.

Work Experience

Freelance Web Developer 2023 - 2024

Freelance and Open For Works

- Develop and maintain responsive websites for clients, utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS,
- · Writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices.
- Integrating data from various back-end services and databases.
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical
- Stay plugged into emerging technologies and appling them into projects.

Executive Warehouse Management

2020 - 2023

Ozwin Retailing Sdn Bhd

- Organize and control stocks to ensure inventories are maintained at optimum level consistent with usage requirements.
- Weekly stocks arrangement to all branches
- · Manage and maintain company's E-Commerce sites like Lazada, Shopee, Woocommerce and Shopify
- Manage and update backend database of warehouse daily to ensure stock availability on E-Commerce sites & retail branches.

IT Technician & PC Sale Advisor

2017 - 2020

Stormzone PLT

- Computer hardware installation, troubleshooting and maintenance.
- · Advice and accommodate client for custom builds based on best
- Basic networking
- Closing sales.

Education & Certifications

Full-Stack Web

Development Certificate 2022 - 2023

• Front-End Web Development : HTML, CSS & JS • Front-End Frameworks : JQuery, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS & ReactJS

• Back-End Web Development : NodeJS with ExpressJS

• SQL & NOSQL Databases , API and Version Control

• Authentication and Security - Handling Credentials & Designing Secure Login

Diploma In

Astin College

Management 2014 - 2017

• Business systems, Business ethics and Human resource management

• Forms of business organisations management processes

• Future dimensions of business opportunities in a global economy.

Technical Skills

FRONTEND BACKEND **FRAMEWOKRS** TOOLS HTML NODEJS **REACTJS VSCODE** CSS **PYTHON** NEXTIS GIT & GITHUR JAVASCRIPT MONGODB **JOUERY POSTMAN** TAILWINDCSS MYSOL **PESTICIDE** RESTEUL BOOTSTRAP **EXPRESSIS** CDT

















MONGOOSE

Languages

TECHNICAL JAVASCRIPT : Advanced PYTHON: Intermediate

NON-TECHNICAL ENGLISH: **Bilingual Proficiency** B.MALAYSIA : Native